Guide to the Student Organization Records
University of Houston Libraries
Student Organization Records
1930-2009
2009-020
University of Houston. Student Organizations; University of Houston. Center for Fraternity and Sorority Life; University of Houston. Center for Student Involvement; University of Houston. Council of Ethnic Organizations
53.00 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
The processed records in this collection contain 14 boxes relating to the various student organizations at the University of Houston. A significant portion of this material was given to the archives from the university Print Plant.
Historical Note:
Student organizations have been an important part of the University of Houston since before it was a four-year institution. Student organizations played a considerable role in the overall educational process at what was then called the Houston Junior College (established in 1927), in spite of difficulties of finding time for meetings and activities, of having facilities available, and of stretching already-taut student budgets for even the most modest dues and fees. [1]
The Cougar was actually the first extracurricular activity at HJC, pre-dating the original classes in journalism (which began in 1928-1929 under Fred R. Birney) by a full year. It was both a laboratory for journalism students and a student actiivty. [2]
Other “original” student organizations include a girl’s basketball team, an ice hockey team, the Student Council, The John R. Bender Dramatic Club, the HJC Oratorical Association, the Cougar Collegians, the Girl’s Outdoor Club, the Guild Savant, the Student Association, the Speakers’ Club, the Cougar, and the Houstonian. [3]
Today, the University of Houston is the second most ethnically diverse major research university in the United States. Students come to UH from more than 137 nations and from across the U.S. The student body comprises more than 40,000 undergraduate and graduate students. The diversity of the campus can be seen by the broad range of student organizations that exist. There are approximately 500 student organizations and 16 intercollegiate sports teams. These organizations vary in focus, from political or social, to religious. [4]
The Council of Ethnic Organizations (CEO) is a student-fee funded organization founded in 1972. It works with member organizations to promote cultural awareness, diversity, and inclusion. [6]
The Center for Student Involvement (CSI) helps students develop student organizations, coordinate events, and gain valuable skills in the process. [5]
References:
[1] Patrick J. Nicholson, In Time: An Anecdotal History of the First Fifty Years of the University of Houston (Houston, TX: Pacesetter Press, 1977), 56.
[2] Patrick J. Nicholson, In Time: An Anecdotal History of the First Fifty Years of the University of Houston (Houston, TX: Pacesetter Press, 1977), 59.
[3] Patrick J. Nicholson, In Time: An Anecdotal History of the First Fifty Years of the University of Houston (Houston, TX: Pacesetter Press, 1977), 56.
[4] UH at a Glance, available from http://www.uh.edu/about/uh-glance/, accessed January 6, 2017
[5] Center for Student Involvement http://www.uh.edu/csi/, accessed January 6, 2017
[6] Council of Ethnic Organizations http://www.uh.edu/csiceo/, accessed January 6, 2017
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
University of Houston; University of Houston -- Students; University of Houston. Center for Fraternity and Sorority Life; University of Houston. Center for Student Involvement; University of Houston. Council of Ethnic Organizations
Acquisition Information:
Most materials in Series 1 and 2 were transferred from the University Print Plant. Additional accruals have been transferred to the University Archives by the Council of Ethnic Organizations (July 2011), the Center for Student Involvement (May 2014), and the Center for Fraternity and Sorority Life (May 2014).
Conditions Governing Access:
Series 1-3 are open for research.
Unprocessed materials in Series 4-6 may be restricted and not available for access. For questions about materials in this collection or to request access, contact the curator.
Related Materials:
University of Houston Student Activities bound volumes, 1927-1962
Information about related materials is available at http://library.uh.edu/record=b3922011~S11
Scope and Contents
The processed records in this collection contain 14 boxes relating to the various student organizations at the University of Houston. A significant portion of this material was given to the archives from the university Print Plant. Materials include correspondence, brochures, pamphlets, flyers, club rosters, publications, event programs, and club policies. The bulk of the material consists of records relating to fraternities and sororities on campus; this includes photographs, slides, negatives, and scrapbooks. This collection is arranged alphabetically by organization name, with the fraternity/ sorority records located largely in a separate series. Tau Beta Sigma materials make up a large portion of the collection, and are arranged in their own series. Processed materials range in date from the 1930s to 2009.
Additional materials from the Council of Ethnic Organizations, the Center for Student Involvement, and the Center for Fraternity and Sorority Life were received in 2011 and 2014, and are not yet fully processed. Represented in three "unprocessed" series, these materials date from 1951 to 2014 and consitute an additional 40 linear feet of material.
Detailed List of Contents
- Student Organizations Arranged Alphabetically
  - Achievement Rewards for College Scientists (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A.D. Bruce Religion Center (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Humanics Student Association (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Student Union (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Black Student Union (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Campus Leaders (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cap & Gown Senior Women’s Honorary Society (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Catholic Newman Association (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chinese American Citizen’s Alliance Youth Club (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Christian Science Organization (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Club Managers Association (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - College and University Personnel Association (C.U.P.A.) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Collegiate Council for the United Nations (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cougar Capers (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cougar Executives Organization (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Council of Ethnic Organizations (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gay, Lesbian, & Bisexual Alliance (G.L.O.B.A.L.) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Good News Gospel Choir (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Hillel (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Homecoming (Box 1, Folder 19a)
  - Honors Day Flyers/Programs (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Honors Day Luncheon Invitations (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Hotel Sales Management Association (H.S.M.A.) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - International Student Organization (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Lutheran Campus Ministry (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - M&M’s (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Methodist Wesley Foundation (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Methodist Wesley Foundation “Lamp Lighter” (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Methodist Wesley Foundation “the Wesleyan” (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Volunteer Program (M.V.P) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous (Student Organization) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - National Society of Scabbard and Blade (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Newman Club (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - New English Club (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Par Excellence (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Pep Club (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Postal Services, Presbyterian Campus Christian Life (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Presbyterian Student Association (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Religious Activities (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Religious Activities (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Religious Groups Council (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sailing Club (Box 1, Folder 41-43)
  - Scholar’s Community (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Society of Engineers (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Spirits & Sparks (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Student Association (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Student Association, Correspondence & Budget (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Student Association - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Student Association - Peer Tutorial Service (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Student Association - Student Gov. “Cougar Paw”, 1956, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Student association - Student Gov. Student Senate (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Student Opportunity Service (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Student Publications - “The Daily Cougar” (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Student Publications - Humor/Comics (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Student Publications - “The Houstonian” (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Student Publications - Mappa Mundi (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Student Publications - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Student Publications - Personnel (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Student Publications - Student Publications Committee (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Student Publications - Style Book (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Student Publications - "The SPB Cinema Committee Tabloid", 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Student Publications - "The SNI Alternative", 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Student Publications - "The Process", 1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sunday Evening Club, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Sunday Evening Club, “20 years” (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Texas Public Interest Research Group (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Quadrangle (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Staff Club (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 20 Year Men’s Club, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 20 Year Men’s Club, 1950s (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 20 Years Men’s Club, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 20 Years Men’s Club, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 20 Years Men’s Club, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 20 Years Men’s Club - Group Photos (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 20 Years Men’s Club - Newspaper Clipping (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The University Club (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - University Festival (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - University of Houston Rodeo Association (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Upward Bound (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - World Council (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Young Socialist Alliance (Y.S.A) (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Fraternities and Sororities Arranged Alphabetically
  - Acacia Fraternity, Intro. to Acacia & the laws (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Alpha Chi Omega (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Alpha Chi Sigma (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Alpha Epsilon Delta (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi - Pledge Manual (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Alpha Epsilon Rho (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Alpha Gamma, 1983, 1984, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Alpha Lambda Delta - Honoraries, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Alpha Phi Omega - Pledge Manual 1946, Student Directory (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Alpha Psi Omega - Original Members (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Alpha Psi Omega - Playbill, September 1933, September 1934 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Alpha Psi Omega - Playbill, 1938, 1947, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Alpha Psi Omega - Playbill, 1957, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Alpha Psi Omega - Playbill, 1961, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Alpha Sigma Phi - Publicity for the Fraternity (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Alpha Sigma Tau - 1955 New Year’s Eve Dance (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Alpha Phi Omega (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Beta Sigma Phi (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Chi Epsilon (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Delta Chi - Constitution & by-laws, Manuals, 1953, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Delta Gamma Fraternity - Stationery & Invitations (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Delta Psi Kappa (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Delta Psi Omega (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Delta Sigma Phi - Positive Scholarship Program (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Delta Sigma Phi - (Delta Theta petition to Delta Sigma Phi) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Delta Sigma Phi - Constitution adopted September 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Delta Sigma Pi (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Delta Sigma Theta - Delta May 1971, Invitations (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Delta Theta (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Delta Theta Phi (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Fraternity Newspaper Clippings (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gamma Alpha Chi - Invitations (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gamma Nu - Job Descriptions (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Alumni/Membership Rosters (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Blank Forms (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Department Heads Meeting (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Fraternity Handbook (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - The Greek Bulletin, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - The Greek Bulletin, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - The Greek Messenger, 2/1/1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - I.F.C. Handbook, Fall semester, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - L.S. Mitchell Files (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - L.S. Mitchell - Handbook Files (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - L.S. Mitchell - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - L.S. Mitchell - Plays/ Stories (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - L.S. Mitchell Files - Scholarship App. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Meeting Minutes (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - National Frat. Correspondence, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Special Events - Convocation (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Special Events - Greek Week (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Special Events - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council - Stationery (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Kappa Alpha - Chapter Files (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Kappa Alpha - Laws, December 1947 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Kappa Alpha - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Kappa Alpha - Number 1’s Handbook, February 15, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Kappa Alpha - Scholarship (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Kappa Delta Pi - Invitations (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi - Banquet, March 23, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Lamda Chi Alpha - Constitution and Statutory Code (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Omega Psi Phi - Texas Tee-Off - Classic Poster (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa - Society (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Panhellenic - Annual Workshop, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Panhellenic - City Notices (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Panhellenic - Handbooks, 1958-1971 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Panhellenic - Letters to prosp. Blank Rush Info. (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Panhellenic - Posters (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Panhellenic - Sorority Info. Flyers (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Panhellenic - Special Events - Invitations (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Phi Alpha Delta (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Phi Beta (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Phi Beta Delta (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Phi Delta Chi (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Phi Delta Kappa (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Phi Delta Phi (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Phi Gamma Nu (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Phi Epsilon Phi - Constitution & By-Laws (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Phi Eta Sigma - Forum, Flyer, Invitations, 1969, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Pi Delta Sorority scrapbook, 1939-1955 (Box 14, Item 1)
  - Phi Delta Chi (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Phi Kappa - Constitutions & By-Laws, September 9, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - Constitutions & By-Laws, 1950, 1966, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - Initiation, Banquet, Programs (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - Letters to Faculty (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - Special Event Invitations (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Phi Kappa Phi - Stationery (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma - Book of Laws, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma - Songbook, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma - Membership Directory, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Phi Kappa Theta - 1960 Directory, Pledge Manual 1961, Special Events (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Phi Mu (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Phi Rho Pi (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa - Outline for Pledge Education, 1951, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa - Programmed Services, Miscellaneous, August 1949 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Phi Theta Kappa - National Convention, Stationery, April 22, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Phi Upsilon Omioron (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Pi Delta sorority directories, 1952-1956 (Box 4, Folder 18a)
  - Pi Delta Epsilon (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Pi Delta Phi - 2nd Annual Report, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Memebership Rosters, 1955-1959, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Petition to Pi Kappa Alpha from Sigma Alpha Chi (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Accounting Records, Contracts (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Blank Forms, Blank Roll Book (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Cash Records, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Fraternities at Univ. of Houston (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Fraternity Manual, 1952 Revision (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Natl. Inter-Fraternity Conference, yearbook, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Newspaper Clipping, Photos (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - “Phi Delta Kappa” (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Resume of the History of Pi Kappa Alpha (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Rosters (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Rule, By-Laws, Policies, Songs (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - “Shield and Diamond”, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Special Events Invitation (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - Stationery (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - The Forensic May 1971, Debate Tournament (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha - The Star & Lamp February 1956 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Pi Omega Pi (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Pi Sigma Epsilon (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Pi Tau Sigma (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Psi Chi - (Psychology Club), The Inkblot, December 2, 1957-April 29, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Rush Guides (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon - National Law, Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu - Flyer, Octagonal, Winter 1996, Spring 1997 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Sigma Chi - Derby Day Flyer, Constitution & Statutes, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Annual Convention Info. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Board of Directories, Meeting Notes (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - 1959 Convention Reports (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Enrollment and Remittance Forms (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Financial Records (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Gene Robbing (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - General Info (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - 1st-3rd Interview Report (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Members List (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Newsletters (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Newspaper clippings (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Sigma Delta Chi - Special Event Flyers & Programs (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Sigma Delta Tau (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sigma Gamma Epsilon (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sigma Gamma Rho (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Sigma Iota Epsilon (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Sigma Iota Epsilon - The Managers Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Sigma Iota Epsilon - Newsletters (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Sigma Iota Epsilon - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Sigma Iota Epsilon - Constitution, revisions, proofs (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Sigma Nu (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon - Book of Laws, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Sigma Phi Omega (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sigma Phi - Manual, Laws (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sigma Xi - Petition for establishment of a Chapter, April 1965 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Sigma Xi - Information for Executive Committee March 1963 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sigma Xi - Invitations, Certificate (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Sigma Xi - Member Profile (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Sigma Xi - The Role & Scope, Nominations for Membership Form (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon - The Black Book, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Tau Omega Alpha (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Theta Chi - The Manual (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Theta Sigma Phi (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Theta Xi (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Tau Beta Sigma
  - Files
    - 35th Anniversary, A Continuous Celebration of Music (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Active Membership Dues, Fall 1984-Spring 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Basic Rules of Parliamentary Procedures (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Calendar of Events, active list, Pledge rules, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Candidate Forms (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Summary Report, June 27, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Color Guard Programs, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Color Guard Program, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Color Guard Program, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, from Stevo, September 7, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Cougar Band-Aid, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cougar Band Handbook, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cougar Band Handbook, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Cougar Band Handbook, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cougar Band Handbook, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Cougar Band Handbook, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Cougar Band Directory, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Cougar Band Student Directory, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Cougar Band - S.W. District Convention Bid (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Houston Cougar Band - Decals (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Houston Cougar Band - Logo (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Initiate Registration (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Invitations/Announcements (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Jewelry Orders (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - National Convention, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - NW State University (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Officers & Committees, Loyalty Song (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Requisition for Funding (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Sales & Receipts (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - San Jacinto Day, April 21, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - SW District Convention - San Angelo, TX., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - SW District Convention - Information, Houston, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - SW District Convention - Texas Christian University, Fort Worth, TX (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Texas Lutheran College, Area Workshop, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Texas Tech Informational Kit, SW District, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Treasures Report (Box 6, Folder 46)